A Guide to the William Ingham Papers, 1945-2013: SC 0002
Special Collections, Carrier Library, James Madison University
- Series 12: Subject Files, 1992-2013
  - Motion and Flow, 1992, undated (Box 112, Folder 9)
  - Pestroika – Restructuring (folder 1 of 2), 1996, 1998-1999, undated (Box 112, Folder 10)
  - Pestroika – Restructuring (folder 2 of 2), 1996, 1998-1999, undated (Box 112, Folder 11)
  - Physics Department 94-95, 1994-1995, undated (Box 112, Folder 12)
  - Physics Department 95-96 (folder 1 of 2), 1993-1996, undated (Box 112, Folder 13)
  - Physics Department 95-96 (folder 2 of 2), 1993-1996, undated (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Physics Department 96-97, 1996-1997 (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - Physics Program Revisions, 1995-1996, undated (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Promotion and Tenure, 1992 (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Reconciliation Committee, 1999 (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Recruiting Students and Graduates, 1995-1996, undated (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Restructuring Plan Review, 1994 (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - Robinette v. JMU, 1992-1993 (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - SACS Report, 1995 (Box 113, Folder 9)
  - Strategic Plan 95-96, 1995-1996, undated (Box 113, Folder 10)
  - Strategic Plan 97-98, 1997-1998 (Box 113, Folder 11)
  - TBS, 1995, undated (Box 113, Folder 12)
  - UMSC Course Development, 1994-1995, undated (Box 113, Folder 13)
  - Visualizing Information, 1992, undated (Box 113, Folder 14)
  - VPAA Search, 1998-2000, undated (Box 113, Folder 15)
  - VPAA Search – Request for Nominations, 1998-2000 (Box 113, Folder 16)
- Series 13: Media, 1992-2012
  No particular arrangement.
  This last series contains various types of media including one 3.5" floppy disk, four compact discs, one audio cassette, and one USB flash drive (returned to donor). All media types are in the process of being digitized as of June 2016. Access to content will be made available once digitization is complete, barring any copyright or other use restrictions.
  - Various media (in-process), 1992-2012 (Box XX)